Contact

mckinnmonavie@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ashleemckinney-b8078011a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing

Hospitals

Emergency Nursing Pediatric Course (ENPC)

Certifications

ACLS: Advanced Cardiovascular Life Support

Ashlee McKinney

Nurse Administrator/House Supervisor at Methodist Specialty and Transplant Hospital

San Antonio, Texas Area

Summary

Graduated from high school 1994. Started attending college at College of Southern Idaho 1994, graduated with an Associate of Art's Degree 1996. Attended Boise State University where I graduated with my BSN in 2002. My first hospital job was with St Lukes Hospital where I worked as a nurse apprentice in the ER while attending nursing school at BSU in 1999. -2010 in ED Worked my first 3 years as a nurse apprentice while in nursing school.

Hired as RN when I graduated from nursing school in 2002-2010. Left to follow my dreams as a travel RN.

Travel ER RN for 7 years through Parallon Workforce Management Solutions. My husband and I both worked as travel RN's and worked assignments throughout various states within the US. (Texas, Idaho, Utah, Big Island of Hawai'i, Oahu)

Last year my husband, our 3 boys and I decided to settle down again, however this time in Texas. We love the warmer weather and friendly people. I started working at MSTH as their ER Educator September of 2016 - currently employed with MSTH. I cover the daytime House Supervisor hours, continue to work with the education dept., soon to be teaching ENPC, help administration as needed as well as cover shifts on the ED if needed. I love the career path I chose as an RN. Helping those in need and/or witnessing the positive ways we as RN's impact our patient's lives for the better each and every day; truly priceless.

Experience

Methodist Specialty and Transplant Hospital Nurse Administrator/House Supervisor June 2017 - Present (3 years 1 month)

San Antonio, Texas

Methodist Specialty and Transplant Hospital Emergency Department Educator August 2016 - June 2017 (11 months)

San Antonio, Texas Area

HILO MEDICAL CENTER

Emergency Room Registered Nurse April 2012 - April 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Hilo, Hawaii

Big Island of Hawaii.

Travel ER nurse
Emergency Room Registered Nurse
October 2010 - March 2012 (1 year 6 months)
Parallon Workforce Management Solutions

Travel ER RN:

Northeast Methodist: S.A., TX.
3 travel assignments/contracts
West Valley Medical: Caldwell, ID.
1 travel assignment/contract

Parallon Workforce Solutions
Travel RN
October 2010 - March 2012 (1 year 6 months)
San Antonio Texas, Caldwell Idaho

St. Luke's Health System
Emergency Room Registered Nurse
June 1999 - October 2010 (11 years 5 months)
Boise Idaho

3yrs as a Nurse Apprentice 8yrs as a registered nurse in the ER

Education

Boise State University

Bachelor of Science Nursing: BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1998 - 2002)

College of Southern Idaho

Associate of Arts - AA, Elementary Education and Teaching · (1994 - 1996)